import { IExercise } from '../types/IExercise'

export const exercises: IExercise[] = [
  {
    id: 'ex-1',
    nodeId: '1',
    problem: 'Contains Duplicate',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/contains-duplicate/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/contains-duplicate'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-2',
    nodeId: '1',
    problem: 'Valid Anagram',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-anagram/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/valid-anagram'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-3',
    nodeId: '1',
    problem: 'Two Sum',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/two-sum/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/two-sum'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-4',
    nodeId: '1',
    problem: 'Group Anagrams',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/group-anagrams/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/group-anagrams'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-5',
    nodeId: '1',
    problem: 'Top K Frequent Elements',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/top-k-frequent-elements/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/top-k-frequent-elements'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-6',
    nodeId: '1',
    problem: 'Encode and Decode Strings',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/encode-and-decode-strings/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/encode-and-decode-strings'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-7',
    nodeId: '1',
    problem: 'Product of Array Except Self',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/product-of-array-except-self/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/product-of-array-except-self'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-8',
    nodeId: '1',
    problem: 'Valid Sudoku',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-sudoku/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/valid-sudoku'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-9',
    nodeId: '1',
    problem: 'Longest Consecutive Sequence',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-consecutive-sequence/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-consecutive-sequence'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-10',
    nodeId: '2',
    problem: 'Valid Palindrome',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-palindrome/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/valid-palindrome'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-11',
    nodeId: '2',
    problem: 'Two Sum II Input Array Is Sorted',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/two-sum-ii-input-array-is-sorted/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/two-sum-ii-input-array-is-sorted'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-12',
    nodeId: '2',
    problem: '3Sum',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/3sum/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/3sum'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-13',
    nodeId: '2',
    problem: 'Container With Most Water',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/container-with-most-water/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/container-with-most-water'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-14',
    nodeId: '2',
    problem: 'Trapping Rain Water',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/trapping-rain-water/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/trapping-rain-water'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-15',
    nodeId: '3',
    problem: 'Valid Parentheses',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-parentheses/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/valid-parentheses'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-16',
    nodeId: '3',
    problem: 'Min Stack',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/min-stack/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/min-stack'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-17',
    nodeId: '3',
    problem: 'Evaluate Reverse Polish Notation',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/evaluate-reverse-polish-notation/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/evaluate-reverse-polish-notation'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-18',
    nodeId: '3',
    problem: 'Generate Parentheses',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/generate-parentheses/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/generate-parentheses'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-19',
    nodeId: '3',
    problem: 'Daily Temperatures',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/daily-temperatures/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/daily-temperatures'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-20',
    nodeId: '3',
    problem: 'Car Fleet',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/car-fleet/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/car-fleet'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-21',
    nodeId: '3',
    problem: 'Largest Rectangle In Histogram',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/largest-rectangle-in-histogram/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/largest-rectangle-in-histogram'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-22',
    nodeId: '4',
    problem: 'Binary Search',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-search/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/binary-search'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-23',
    nodeId: '4',
    problem: 'Search a 2D Matrix',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/search-a-2d-matrix/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/search-a-2d-matrix'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-24',
    nodeId: '4',
    problem: 'Koko Eating Bananas',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/koko-eating-bananas/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/koko-eating-bananas'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-25',
    nodeId: '4',
    problem: 'Find Minimum In Rotated Sorted Array',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/find-minimum-in-rotated-sorted-array/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/find-minimum-in-rotated-sorted-array'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-26',
    nodeId: '4',
    problem: 'Search In Rotated Sorted Array',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/search-in-rotated-sorted-array/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/search-in-rotated-sorted-array'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-27',
    nodeId: '4',
    problem: 'Time Based Key Value Store',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/time-based-key-value-store/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/time-based-key-value-store'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-28',
    nodeId: '4',
    problem: 'Median of Two Sorted Arrays',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/median-of-two-sorted-arrays/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/median-of-two-sorted-arrays'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-29',
    nodeId: '5',
    problem: 'Best Time to Buy And Sell Stock',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-30',
    nodeId: '5',
    problem: 'Longest Substring Without Repeating Characters',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-substring-without-repeating-characters/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-substring-without-repeating-characters'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-31',
    nodeId: '5',
    problem: 'Longest Repeating Character Replacement',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-repeating-character-replacement/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-repeating-character-replacement'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-32',
    nodeId: '5',
    problem: 'Permutation in String',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/permutation-in-string/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/permutation-in-string'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-33',
    nodeId: '5',
    problem: 'Minimum Window Substring',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-window-substring/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/minimum-window-substring'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-34',
    nodeId: '5',
    problem: 'Sliding Window Maximum',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/sliding-window-maximum/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/sliding-window-maximum'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-35',
    nodeId: '6',
    problem: 'Reverse Linked List',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-linked-list/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/reverse-linked-list'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-36',
    nodeId: '6',
    problem: 'Merge Two Sorted Lists',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-two-sorted-lists/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/merge-two-sorted-lists'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-37',
    nodeId: '6',
    problem: 'Reorder List',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/reorder-list/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/reorder-list'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-38',
    nodeId: '6',
    problem: 'Remove Nth Node From End of List',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/remove-nth-node-from-end-of-list/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/remove-nth-node-from-end-of-list'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-39',
    nodeId: '6',
    problem: 'Copy List With Random Pointer',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/copy-list-with-random-pointer/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/copy-list-with-random-pointer'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-40',
    nodeId: '6',
    problem: 'Add Two Numbers',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/add-two-numbers/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/add-two-numbers'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-41',
    nodeId: '6',
    problem: 'Linked List Cycle',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/linked-list-cycle/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/linked-list-cycle'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-42',
    nodeId: '6',
    problem: 'Find The Duplicate Number',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-duplicate-number/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/find-the-duplicate-number'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-43',
    nodeId: '6',
    problem: 'LRU Cache',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/lru-cache/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/lru-cache'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-44',
    nodeId: '6',
    problem: 'Merge K Sorted Lists',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-k-sorted-lists/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/merge-k-sorted-lists'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-45',
    nodeId: '6',
    problem: 'Reverse Nodes In K Group',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-nodes-in-k-group/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/reverse-nodes-in-k-group'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-46',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Invert Binary Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/invert-binary-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/invert-binary-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-47',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Maximum Depth of Binary Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-depth-of-binary-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/maximum-depth-of-binary-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-48',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Diameter of Binary Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/diameter-of-binary-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/diameter-of-binary-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-49',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Balanced Binary Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/balanced-binary-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/balanced-binary-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-50',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Same Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/same-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/same-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-51',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Subtree of Another Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/subtree-of-another-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/subtree-of-another-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-52',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Lowest Common Ancestor of a Binary Search Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/lowest-common-ancestor-of-a-binary-search-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/lowest-common-ancestor-of-a-binary-search-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-53',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Binary Tree Level Order Traversal',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-level-order-traversal/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/binary-tree-level-order-traversal'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-54',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Binary Tree Right Side View',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-right-side-view/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/binary-tree-right-side-view'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-55',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Count Good Nodes In Binary Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/count-good-nodes-in-binary-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/count-good-nodes-in-binary-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-56',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Validate Binary Search Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/validate-binary-search-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/validate-binary-search-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-57',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Kth Smallest Element In a Bst',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-smallest-element-in-a-bst/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/kth-smallest-element-in-a-bst'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-58',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Construct Binary Tree From Preorder And Inorder Traversal',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/construct-binary-tree-from-preorder-and-inorder-traversal/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/construct-binary-tree-from-preorder-and-inorder-traversal'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-59',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Binary Tree Maximum Path Sum',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-maximum-path-sum/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/binary-tree-maximum-path-sum'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-60',
    nodeId: '7',
    problem: 'Serialize And Deserialize Binary Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/serialize-and-deserialize-binary-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/serialize-and-deserialize-binary-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-61',
    nodeId: '8',
    problem: 'Implement Trie Prefix Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-trie-prefix-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/implement-trie-prefix-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-62',
    nodeId: '8',
    problem: 'Design Add And Search Words Data Structure',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/design-add-and-search-words-data-structure/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/design-add-and-search-words-data-structure'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-63',
    nodeId: '8',
    problem: 'Word Search II',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/word-search-ii/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/word-search-ii'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-64',
    nodeId: '9',
    problem: 'Subsets',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/subsets/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/subsets'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-65',
    nodeId: '9',
    problem: 'Combination Sum',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/combination-sum/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/combination-sum'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-66',
    nodeId: '9',
    problem: 'Permutations',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/permutations/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/permutations'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-67',
    nodeId: '9',
    problem: 'Subsets II',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/subsets-ii/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/subsets-ii'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-68',
    nodeId: '9',
    problem: 'Combination Sum II',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/combination-sum-ii/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/combination-sum-ii'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-69',
    nodeId: '9',
    problem: 'Word Search',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/word-search/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/word-search'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-70',
    nodeId: '9',
    problem: 'Palindrome Partitioning',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/palindrome-partitioning/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/palindrome-partitioning'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-71',
    nodeId: '9',
    problem: 'Letter Combinations of a Phone Number',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/letter-combinations-of-a-phone-number/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/letter-combinations-of-a-phone-number'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-72',
    nodeId: '9',
    problem: 'N Queens',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/n-queens/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/n-queens'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-73',
    nodeId: '10',
    problem: 'Kth Largest Element In a Stream',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-a-stream/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/kth-largest-element-in-a-stream'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-74',
    nodeId: '10',
    problem: 'Last Stone Weight',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/last-stone-weight/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/last-stone-weight'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-75',
    nodeId: '10',
    problem: 'K Closest Points to Origin',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/k-closest-points-to-origin/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/k-closest-points-to-origin'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-76',
    nodeId: '10',
    problem: 'Kth Largest Element In An Array',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-an-array/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/kth-largest-element-in-an-array'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-77',
    nodeId: '10',
    problem: 'Task Scheduler',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/task-scheduler/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/task-scheduler'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-78',
    nodeId: '10',
    problem: 'Design Twitter',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/design-twitter/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/design-twitter'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-79',
    nodeId: '10',
    problem: 'Find Median From Data Stream',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/find-median-from-data-stream/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/find-median-from-data-stream'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-80',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Number of Islands',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-islands/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/number-of-islands'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-81',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Max Area of Island',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/max-area-of-island/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/max-area-of-island'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-82',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Clone Graph',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/clone-graph/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/clone-graph'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-83',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Walls And Gates',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/walls-and-gates/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/walls-and-gates'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-84',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Rotting Oranges',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/rotting-oranges/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/rotting-oranges'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-85',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Pacific Atlantic Water Flow',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/pacific-atlantic-water-flow/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/pacific-atlantic-water-flow'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-86',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Surrounded Regions',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/surrounded-regions/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/surrounded-regions'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-87',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Course Schedule',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/course-schedule'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-88',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Course Schedule II',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule-ii/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/course-schedule-ii'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-89',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Graph Valid Tree',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/graph-valid-tree/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/graph-valid-tree'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-90',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Number of Connected Components In An Undirected Graph',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-connected-components-in-an-undirected-graph/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/number-of-connected-components-in-an-undirected-graph'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-91',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Redundant Connection',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/redundant-connection/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/redundant-connection'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-92',
    nodeId: '11',
    problem: 'Word Ladder',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/word-ladder/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/word-ladder'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-93',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'Climbing Stairs',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/climbing-stairs/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/climbing-stairs'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-94',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'Min Cost Climbing Stairs',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/min-cost-climbing-stairs/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/min-cost-climbing-stairs'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-95',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'House Robber',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/house-robber/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/house-robber'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-96',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'House Robber II',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/house-robber-ii/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/house-robber-ii'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-97',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'Longest Palindromic Substring',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-palindromic-substring/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-palindromic-substring'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-98',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'Palindromic Substrings',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/palindromic-substrings/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/palindromic-substrings'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-99',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'Decode Ways',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/decode-ways/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/decode-ways'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-100',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'Coin Change',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/coin-change/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/coin-change'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-101',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'Maximum Product Subarray',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-product-subarray/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/maximum-product-subarray'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-102',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'Word Break',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/word-break/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/word-break'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-103',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'Longest Increasing Subsequence',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-increasing-subsequence/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-increasing-subsequence'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-104',
    nodeId: '12',
    problem: 'Partition Equal Subset Sum',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/partition-equal-subset-sum/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/partition-equal-subset-sum'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-105',
    nodeId: '13',
    problem: 'Insert Interval',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/insert-interval/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/insert-interval'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-106',
    nodeId: '13',
    problem: 'Merge Intervals',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-intervals/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/merge-intervals'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-107',
    nodeId: '13',
    problem: 'Non Overlapping Intervals',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/non-overlapping-intervals/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/non-overlapping-intervals'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-108',
    nodeId: '13',
    problem: 'Meeting Rooms',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/meeting-rooms/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/meeting-rooms'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-109',
    nodeId: '13',
    problem: 'Meeting Rooms II',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/meeting-rooms-ii/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/meeting-rooms-ii'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-110',
    nodeId: '13',
    problem: 'Minimum Interval to Include Each Query',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-interval-to-include-each-query/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/minimum-interval-to-include-each-query'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-111',
    nodeId: '14',
    problem: 'Maximum Subarray',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-subarray/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/maximum-subarray'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-112',
    nodeId: '14',
    problem: 'Jump Game',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/jump-game/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/jump-game'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-113',
    nodeId: '14',
    problem: 'Jump Game II',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/jump-game-ii/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/jump-game-ii'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-114',
    nodeId: '14',
    problem: 'Gas Station',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/gas-station/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/gas-station'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-115',
    nodeId: '14',
    problem: 'Hand of Straights',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/hand-of-straights/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/hand-of-straights'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-116',
    nodeId: '14',
    problem: 'Merge Triplets to Form Target Triplet',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-triplets-to-form-target-triplet/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/merge-triplets-to-form-target-triplet'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-117',
    nodeId: '14',
    problem: 'Partition Labels',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/partition-labels/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/partition-labels'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-118',
    nodeId: '14',
    problem: 'Valid Parenthesis String',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-parenthesis-string/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/valid-parenthesis-string'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-119',
    nodeId: '15',
    problem: 'Reconstruct Itinerary',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/reconstruct-itinerary/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/reconstruct-itinerary'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-120',
    nodeId: '15',
    problem: 'Min Cost to Connect All Points',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/min-cost-to-connect-all-points/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/min-cost-to-connect-all-points'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-121',
    nodeId: '15',
    problem: 'Network Delay Time',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/network-delay-time/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/network-delay-time'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-122',
    nodeId: '15',
    problem: 'Swim In Rising Water',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/swim-in-rising-water/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/swim-in-rising-water'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-123',
    nodeId: '15',
    problem: 'Alien Dictionary',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/alien-dictionary/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/alien-dictionary'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-124',
    nodeId: '15',
    problem: 'Cheapest Flights Within K Stops',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/cheapest-flights-within-k-stops/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/cheapest-flights-within-k-stops'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-125',
    nodeId: '16',
    problem: 'Unique Paths',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/unique-paths/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/unique-paths'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-126',
    nodeId: '16',
    problem: 'Longest Common Subsequence',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-common-subsequence/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-common-subsequence'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-127',
    nodeId: '16',
    problem: 'Best Time to Buy And Sell Stock With Cooldown',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock-with-cooldown/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock-with-cooldown'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-128',
    nodeId: '16',
    problem: 'Coin Change II',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/coin-change-ii/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/coin-change-ii'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-129',
    nodeId: '16',
    problem: 'Target Sum',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/target-sum/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/target-sum'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-130',
    nodeId: '16',
    problem: 'Interleaving String',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/interleaving-string/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/interleaving-string'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-131',
    nodeId: '16',
    problem: 'Longest Increasing Path In a Matrix',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-increasing-path-in-a-matrix/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution:
      'https://neetcode.io/solutions/longest-increasing-path-in-a-matrix'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-132',
    nodeId: '16',
    problem: 'Distinct Subsequences',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/distinct-subsequences/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/distinct-subsequences'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-133',
    nodeId: '16',
    problem: 'Edit Distance',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/edit-distance/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/edit-distance'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-134',
    nodeId: '16',
    problem: 'Burst Balloons',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/burst-balloons/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/burst-balloons'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-135',
    nodeId: '16',
    problem: 'Regular Expression Matching',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/regular-expression-matching/',
    difficulty: 'Hard',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/regular-expression-matching'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-136',
    nodeId: '17',
    problem: 'Single Number',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/single-number/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/single-number'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-137',
    nodeId: '17',
    problem: 'Number of 1 Bits',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-1-bits/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/number-of-1-bits'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-138',
    nodeId: '17',
    problem: 'Counting Bits',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/counting-bits/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/counting-bits'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-139',
    nodeId: '17',
    problem: 'Reverse Bits',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-bits/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/reverse-bits'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-140',
    nodeId: '17',
    problem: 'Missing Number',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/missing-number/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/missing-number'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-141',
    nodeId: '17',
    problem: 'Sum of Two Integers',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/sum-of-two-integers/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/sum-of-two-integers'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-142',
    nodeId: '17',
    problem: 'Reverse Integer',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-integer/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/reverse-integer'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-143',
    nodeId: '18',
    problem: 'Rotate Image',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/rotate-image/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/rotate-image'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-144',
    nodeId: '18',
    problem: 'Spiral Matrix',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/spiral-matrix/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/spiral-matrix'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-145',
    nodeId: '18',
    problem: 'Set Matrix Zeroes',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/set-matrix-zeroes/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/set-matrix-zeroes'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-146',
    nodeId: '18',
    problem: 'Happy Number',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/happy-number/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/happy-number'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-147',
    nodeId: '18',
    problem: 'Plus One',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/plus-one/',
    difficulty: 'Easy',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/plus-one'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-148',
    nodeId: '18',
    problem: 'Pow(x, n)',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/powx-n/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/powx-n'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-149',
    nodeId: '18',
    problem: 'Multiply Strings',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/multiply-strings/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/multiply-strings'
  },
  {
    id: 'ex-150',
    nodeId: '18',
    problem: 'Detect Squares',
    link: 'https://leetcode.com/problems/detect-squares/',
    difficulty: 'Medium',
    solution: 'https://neetcode.io/solutions/detect-squares'
  }
]
